mixthatdrink.com 2019-07-21

# Privacy | Mix That Drink

Your privacy is critically important to us. At MixThatDrink we have a few fundamental principles:

We don’t ask you for personal information. Period.

If you volunteer personal information (say, you email us, so now we have your email address) we don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law or protect our rights.

We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services. (We’re mainly talking about IP addresses, data about your browser and/or devices, and any email address you use to access the site.)

We aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

If you have any questions, please use the [Contact Form](https://mixthatdrink.com/contact/).

### Routine logging

Like most websites, MixThatDrink automatically collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, IP address, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. We do this in order to better understand how our visitors use our website. MixThatDrink may occasionally release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

MixThatDrink also collects potentially personally-identifying information such as the Internet Protocol (IP) addresses of visitors. MixThatDrink needs this information in order to diagnose and troubleshoot problems with the site; to better understand its visitors and how they use our website; and, when necessary, to block abusive visitors such as spammers or malware distributors. This information is shared with our analytics software providers, Google Analytics and Clicky. Please review [How Google uses information from sites or apps that use our services](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/). IP addresses are visible to site administrators when you leave a comment and in our analytics software. MixThatDrink uses [Clicky Web Analytics](https://clicky.com/) to log and analyze the traffic to our web site. You may review Clicky’s privacy policy [here](http://clicky.com/terms/privacy). A “Unique ID” tracking cookie is used for the “legitimate purpose” of identifying unique visitors, but otherwise no “personal data” is logged.

MixThatDrink does not share any of the foregoing information with anyone except to comply with the law or protect our rights.

### Submitted Personal Information

If you leave a blog comment on MixThatDrink, you will be required to share an email address and IP address with us. This information will not be visible on the site. Site administrators will be able to see it. This information is stored in our database. You may use a [SpamGourmet temporary email address](https://www.spamgourmet.com/index.pl) so that MixThatDrink will never see your real email address.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

MixThatDrink discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on MixThatDrink’s behalf or to provide services available at MixThatDrink’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using MixThatDrink’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. MixThatDrink will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations, as described above, MixThatDrink discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when MixThatDrink believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of MixThatDrink, third parties or the public at large. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. MixThatDrink takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

We also may be required to disclose an individual’s personal information in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

MixThatDrink acknowledges that all individuals have the right to access the personal information/data that we maintain about them. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data, should direct his query to mixy[at]mixthatdrink[dot]com. If requested to remove data, we will respond within a reasonable timeframe, not to exceed one week.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. MixThatDrink uses cookies to help MixThatDrink identify and track visitors, their usage of the MixThatDrink website, and their website access preferences. MixThatDrink visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using MixThatDrink’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of MixThatDrink’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

 **Display Ads**

MixThatDrink uses outside ad companies to display ads on the site. These ads may contain cookies. Cookies received with these ads are collected by the third party companies, and we do not have access to this information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit [this page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp#) where you can opt out of certain types of advertising. MixThatDrink is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

MixThatDrink uses Mediavine to manage all third-party advertising on the Website. Mediavine serves content and advertisements when you visit the Website, which may use cookies. Mediavine may collect IP addresses and location to serve personalized ads.  If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices to opt-in or opt-out of this data collection, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

AdWords Remarketing is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by Google. It connects the website visitor activity on mixthatdrink.com with the Google Adwords advertising network. AdWords remarketing will display relevant ads on sites across the Internet, tailored to you based on what parts of the MixThatDrink website you have viewed by placing a cookie on your machine. Third-party vendors, including Google, use these cookies to serve the ads. You can opt out of the cookie tracking here: <http://google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en>.

With respect to Ad Servers: in order to bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of:

www.google.com/adsense  
www.google.com/analytics  
www.clicky.com  
www.amazon.com  
www.cj.com  
www.shareasale.com  
www.linkshare.com  
www.target.com

 **External Links**

MixThatDrink contains links to other sites. MixThatDrink is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

 **Social Sharing**

MixThatDrink embeds a Facebook widget to allow you to see number of likes/shares/recommends and “like/share/recommend” our webpages. This widget may collect your IP address, your web browser User Agent, store and retrieve cookies on your browser, embed additional tracking, and monitor your interaction with the widget, including correlating your Facebook account with whatever action you take within the widget (such as “liking/sharing/recommending” our webpage), if you are logged in to Facebook. For more information about how this data may be used, please see Facebook’s data privacy policy: https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update

MixThatDrink uses a Twitter Tweet widget at our website. As a result, our website makes requests to Twitter’s servers for you to be able to tweet our webpages using your Twitter account. These requests make your IP address visible to Twitter, who may use it in accordance with their data privacy policy: https://twitter.com/en/privacy#update

MixThatDrink uses the Pinterest Save widget at our website to allow you to pin images to Pinterest from our webpages. These requests may track your IP address in accordance with their data privacy policy: https://policy.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy

MixThatDrink uses StumbleUpon Badge widget at our website which may log information when you interact with the widget. Log Data is a form of Non-Identifying Information, in accordance with their privacy policy: http://www.stumbleupon.com/privacy

 **Security**  
MixThatDrink has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

 **Children’s Information**  
MixThatDrink believes it is important to provide added protection for children online. MixThatDrink encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in and/or monitor and guide their online activity. MixThatDrink does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that MixThatDrink has in its database the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please [contact us immediately](https://blogaliving.com/contact/) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, MixThatDrink may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in MixThatDrink’s sole discretion. MixThatDrink will notify clients by making the changes on this privacy page.

 _Last updated March 23, 2018_
